Guide to the Democratic Socialists of America Records TAM.105
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Records: Three scrapbooks: Harrington photos, Justice for All campaign, 1987; Workers Party reports, 1940s; issues of Days of Decision, 1980s; about a dozen audiocassettes, 1980s, probably Harrington talks, 1940-1989 (Box 109)
- Records: Conventions, 1991, 93, 99; Feminist Commission, 1991-92; National Political Committee, Steering Committee, 1994; Key Lists, 1994; Budget Committee, 1991; Correspondence, 1994 (including Member Correspondence), 1991-1999 (Box 110)
- Records: Political Committee, 9/97; Convention, 1997; National Office Committee, 1992-93; Housing Task Force, 1989; Organization Manual; Progressive Student Network, 1980s; Topical files containing circulars, reports, etc., 1980s-1997 (Box 111)
- Records: Political Committee, 1994, 2004, Conventions, 1995-2005; Socialist International, 2001; Computer discs, 3x5, undated, unlabeled, 1994-2005 (Box 112)
- Records: Videocassettes: Michael Harrington, New Directions, 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 113)
- Records: Audio (undated): Billy Bragg, Pete Seeger: Songs of Protest; Letter of Critical Endorsement to the 13th World Youth Festival, 1989; Youth Section: Key Lists, Chapters, Internatioanl Union of Socialist Youth, Young Women's Project; Faculty Mailing, 1993; Anti-War Work, 1991, 1989-1993 (Box 114)
- Photographs: Washington DC Conference; Reproductive Freedom; Activist Individual; Civil Rights March, Boston; DSA/DSOC Conference, NAM; DSCO Board; Freeze March, New York City; U.S. Foreign Relations Policy; Mike and Barbara; Democratic Agenda; DSOC Convention; DSA/DSOC Local Action; Democracy; Democratic Agenda; Convention; DSA Youth Conference; Palme Reception; FRAMES; Solidarity Day; Eurosocialism; DSA Unity Convention; DSA Unity Convention; March on Washington; Democratic Agenda:; Staff/Office; Wimpy; Convention; File in Graphics/Photo Files; Chicago; Jeffrey D. Gold; 31/7 1/E’s Vol. 2; We Are Demo Soc w/A Vision; Art DC Millennium; Michael Harrington Event at Roseland for D.S.A.; Michael Harrington w/celebs; Socialism Past and Future; Michael Harrington; “Tribute Photographs”; “National Board ”; “Some scenes from the Youth Section”; International Union of Socialist Youth World Festival, circa 1975-1999 (Box 115)